So module four, offer building, understanding that value is more important than the actual product. And going into this a little further, result plus time plus effort removed plus proof.
This is, this is a perfect formula. Let's say the service is driveway contracting, I'm going to try to use different examples throughout this course. Don't hold me to it, I might continue using I build websites too often, we're going to go left field here, and I make driveways as a contractor, right?
The result is you're going to have a much more beautiful driveway in two weeks. And you don't have to do anything, you don't have to lift a finger, you don't have to buy materials, you don't have to understand what we're doing, you don't have to understand why your driveway is a little bit more difficult than your neighbor's driveway. And here's my portfolio. Done.
That is the perfect formula for you to perfectly speak to your customer. Right? Be specific about the outcome, you're going to have a, I don't know the verbiage at all. So since I just made this up, you're going to have the perfect crosshatch driveway with bricks counterclockwise, and your car is going to spin in the driveway. So you don't have to, you know, you turn in and out. I don't know, just making these things up.
Address the biggest objection or pain point immediately. If you're talking to customers all the time, you're going to understand what their objections are. It's going to take too long, the noise, how, what color is it? I don't know. I don't know the pain points for driveway contracting.
But you should understand what your customer's objections and pain points are going to be before you even get on the call. If this is part of your learning process, you should be understanding your customer more by hitting that cold call button. Right?
This is proof mechanism, the how that makes it believable. This is the look at our portfolio of ones we've done. Look at the material that you can choose from. Look at the timeline for service A, service B, and service C if you want to add on to your service.
It is not just, this is going to take a week. It's going to take a week if we do this. It's going to take three weeks if we include this. So they understand, or more importantly, the customer is not just deciding between, should I trust these people? Should I go with a competitor?
They are now choosing between which one of your services is more likely for them to choose. They're not deciding, should I choose them? Or should I choose competitor? They're now like, which service of theirs should I choose? Way better spot to be in.
So here are examples of packaging types. Understand from start here all the way to, you know, the retainer. These are different types, so to speak. And depending on your service, this will fit anywhere. Right? Um, you know, if you're selling software, it might be ongoing payment. Uh, it might be just
going back to our driveway service, the sprint. Three packaged offer examples. Um, we are going to audit, uh, your Google profile. We are going to build you a landing page plus a calendar. And this is more like, um, I guess more like lead specific businesses. And we are going to do a UGC ad sprint. So this is going to be, um,
um, type of content that you're going to help your business out with, right? I like the, this slide here, risk reversal and proof strategies. You want to give them some sort of guarantee. And this doesn't mean if we don't do it in three weeks, we give you your money back. It could just mean, um, if we don't hit our timeline, it's free afterwards, right? It doesn't always have to be a
money back. But you can think about what your guarantee might be because your customer more than likely is going to ask for it. Um, be specific about your portfolio. Before and after is always helpful. Um, even as simple as a screenshot of the existing customer conversation. Go through what it might look like for their specific use case.
Um, this is what your driveway used to look like. This is what it can look like. Use AI software, um, use other portfolios that might be similar to them. This is going back to that repeatable process, right?
And then small commitments, get them to lower that barrier to entry. Instead of pitching that 2k retainer, sell a $250 audit or roadmap. Um, instead of going all the way and saying, we will fix all of your driveway. Just say, Hey, we're going to start slow maybe. And talk through exactly what materials you need for this job.
And we're going to have. And we're going to have that conversation for free. Okay. And then you're kind of easing their way into the sale.
And then, uh, going back to that elevator pitch, this shouldn't be an entire 40 minute conversation about the portfolio. It shouldn't be a 40 minute conversation about, um, who they are and how you're differentiating between your competitors.
It shouldn't be a very long spiel. It should be completely quick and complete and quickly understandable by your customer, right? So stop here again, use this worksheet. If you already understand it, great. Move on. If not, literally print this out, put it on your, like right above your monitor and like fill it out and then live by it on all your sales calls.
Pre-offer, pre-call offer scripts, copy paste these. If this is important to you, you haven't already understood it. Here you go. Here's the, here's the winners that we see, right? And how to move quickly.
So just going through what we just went through right here on to the next one.